revive-adserver.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy and Revive Adserver

Privacy and the rights of individuals about how their personal data can be used by companies and other organisations are important and complicated topics.

We want to help you, the user of the Revive Adserver software, get a good understanding of how the Revive Adserver software treats personal data. We also want to provide information about how we treat personal data when you visit this website.

## Personal data in relation to using the Revive Adserver software

As a person or company using the Revive Adserver software, it is important that you are aware of how the software treats personal data. To this end, we have published a number of articles:

  * An article with a brief [description of what GDPR is and how it relates to Revive Adserver](https://www.revive-adserver.com/privacy/gdpr/);
  * An article describing in detail [how the Revive Adserver software treats Personal data](https://www.revive-adserver.com/privacy/personal-data/).

## Personal data in relation to visiting the Revive Adserver website

When you visit this website, you may want to know how we treat your personal data (if any). Please continue reading to learn more.

### Website and company

This is the official website of the Revive Adserver open source project. The website address is www.revive-adserver.com. This website is operated by a not-for-profit company called [Revive Software and Services BV](http://www.revive-sas.com/), incorporated in The Netherlands in 2015.

### Personal data of site visitors

We use Google Analytics to count the number of visits and how often individual web pages are viewed. We enabled the setting in Google Analytics to anonymize IP addresses before processing, so that these statistics can not be traced back to individuals.

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data entered in comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string, as part of our efforts to help spam detection and prevention.

We process information about visitors who comment using the Akismet anti-spam service. The information we collect includes the commenter’s IP address, user agent, referrer, and Site URL (along with other information directly provided by the commenter such as their name, username, email address, and the comment itself).

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture (if any) will visible to the public in the context of your comment.

If you do not want your personal data and profile picture to be visible in a comment on our site, then we recommend not posting that comment to begin with.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you want to leave another comment in the future. These cookies will last for one year.

Cookies will also be set and read by Google Analytics for the purpose of website statistics as described above. These cookies do not contain personal data and use an anonymized IP address, so that they can not be traced back to individuals.

### Protecting our website from malicious activity

The IP address of visitors, and usernames being used in login attempts are logged to check for malicious activity, and to protect our sites from attacks. Examples of conditions when logging occurs include login attempts, requests for suspicious or non-existent URLs. This information is retained for 14 days and is never shared with any third party.

Our sites are part of a network of sites that are actively protected against distributed brute force attacks and other forms of malicious activity. To enable this protection, the IP address of visitors attempting to log into the site is shared with a service provided by ithemes.com. For their privacy policy details, please see the [iThemes Privacy Policy](https://ithemes.com/privacy-policy). It should be noted that we do not have access to any data collected by iThemes, all we receive is the outcome of their analysis about login attempts and their recommendation to block a particular IP address from attempting to access our site (where relevant).
